in inkscape you can combine pathfx I
在Inkscape中，您可以将pathfx i
select the text tool and type some text
选择文本工具并输入一些文本
I will use luckiest guy which is a free
我会用最幸运的人，是免费的
Google font I go to pathfx I see that I
Google字体我转到路径FX，我看到我
need to convert the text to a path to
需要将文本转换为路径
use a path effect
使用路径效果
new in inkscape 1.3 beta is that you can
Inkscape 1.3测试版中的新功能是您可以
do this now with a single click
现在只需点击一下即可完成此操作
so I click on convert text to paths
所以我点击了将文本转换为路径
from the menu I choose perspective
从菜单中我选择透视
envelope
信封
we will look at perspective in the next
我们将在下一篇文章中探讨透视问题
lecture I select envelope deformation I
第一讲信封变形第一讲
click on the Node tool I can now drag
单击我现在可以拖动的节点工具
the Four Corners to deform the shape
使形状变形的四个角
what I want is the end of the text to be
我想要的是文本的结尾是
smaller
更小的
so I hold Ctrl and drag the nodes at the
因此，我按住Ctrl键并将节点拖动到
right end
右端
now I will add a second effect from the
现在，我将添加来自
menu I choose band
菜单我选择乐队
I select edit on canvas I can now curve
我选择了在画布上编辑，现在可以绘制曲线
the text I can switch between the two
我可以在两者之间切换的文本
filters to get the result I want I can
过滤以获得我想要的结果我可以
even change the order of the filters
甚至更改了过滤器的顺序
which will change the look of the shape
这将改变形状的外观
when I'm happy with the shape I'll
当我对这个形状感到满意时，我会
finalize it by going to path object to
通过转到路径对象来完成它
path I will make the text a bit higher I
路径I将使文本更高一些I
call the path text now I go to path
现在我转到路径，将路径称为文本
linked offset
链接偏移
I select the node tool I set the fill
我选择设置填充的结点工具
color to Red I drag the note up I go to
颜色为红色我将便条向上拖到
path object to path I call the path red
路径对象到路径我称该路径为红色
I go to extensions generate from path
我转到从路径生成的扩展
long Shadow I set length to 5. I select
长影我将长度设置为5。我选择
the long Shadow elements and make them a
长影元素并使其成为
single path with Union
具有并集的单路径
I call the path long shadow
我称这条小路为长影
I remove the group folders
我删除组文件夹
in fill and stroke I make the red darker
在填充和笔触中，我把红色变得更深
and inside my text I want a gradient I
在我的文字里，我想要一个渐变
choose linear gradient and I select the
选择线性渐变，然后选择
gradient tool
渐变工具
I make the gradient vertical
我将渐变设置为垂直
I set the gradient to yellow and I make
我将渐变设置为黄色，然后制作
the top color more orange
最上面的颜色更橙色
I convert text to a clip group
我将文本转换为剪辑组
now I'll create a diamond pattern I
现在我将创建一个钻石图案
select the rectangle tool I hold Ctrl
按住Ctrl键选择矩形工具
and drag a small square I go to path
然后拖动一个小方块我走到小路上
object to path I click on the Square
对象指向路径我在正方形上单击
again hold Ctrl and rotate 45 degrees I
再次按住Ctrl并将I旋转45度
go to pathfx from the menu I choose
从我选择的菜单转到pathfx
tiling I set rows to 50 and columns to
平铺I将行数设置为50，列数设置为
150 and I increase the gap between the
150和我之间的差距增加
squares I set offset to 50 I will leave
我将偏移量设置为50的方块，我将离开
the tiling path effect editable I call
我称之为可编辑的平铺路径效果
the path pattern I set the opacity to 15
路径图案我将不透明度设置为15
and the blend mode to multiply I drag
和混合模式，以倍增我拖动
the pattern on the clip group I make the
我制作的剪辑组上的图案
pattern smaller
图案较小
I duplicate text and drag it on top
我复制文本并将其拖到顶部
I shift-click on white and click on the
我按住Shift键并单击白色，然后单击
Red Cross to delete the fill I make the
红十字会删除我的填充物
stroke smaller I call the path stroke
笔划较小我称路径为笔划
white I duplicate stroke white I call
白色I复制笔划白色我称之为白色
the original stroke Shadow I shift click
原始笔划阴影I Shift单击
on black in fill and stroke I set blur
在黑色的填充和笔触上，我设置了模糊
to 10 percent and opacity to 75 percent
到10%，不透明度到75%
I hold alt and position The Shadow
我按住Alt键并定位影子
I duplicate red I make the original Pink
我复制红色，我制作原始的粉色
I call the path pink
我称这条小路为粉色
I position red on the canvas I select
我在我选择的画布上放置红色
the rectangle tool I drag a rectangle
矩形工具我拖出一个矩形
and drag it on the clip group
并将其拖到剪辑组上
I call the path Horizon now I will
我把这条路叫做地平线，现在我会
duplicate long Shadow to make the shadow
复制长阴影以生成阴影
below I call the copy Shadow below I
下面我将复制阴影称为下面的我
place Shadow Below on the bottom and
在下面的底部放置阴影和
click on black
点击黑色
and in fill and stroke I increase the
在填充和笔触中，我增加了
blur
模糊